<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PampangNav</string>
    <string name="left_wing">LeftWing</string>
    <string name="Entrance">Entrance</string>
    <string name="right_wing">RightWing</string>
    <string name="hallway">Hallway</string>
    <string name="add_store_title">Add Store</string>
    <string name="hint_enter_store_name">Enter a store name</string>
    <string name="hint_store_category">Store Category</string>
    <string name="hint_opening_time">Opening Time</string>
    <string name="hint_closing_time">Closing Time</string>
    <string name="button_create">Create</string>
    <string name="open_time_label">Open Time:</string>
    <string name="close_time_label">Close Time:</string>
    <string name="go_to_destination">Go to Destination</string>
    <string name="clear_path">Clear Path</string>
    <string name="login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="buyer">Buyer</string>
    <string name="seller">Seller</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="dont_have_an_account">Dont have an account?</string>
    <string name="register_here">Register Here</string>
    <string name="fragment_seller">Seller</string>
    <string name="fragment_group_chat">Group Chat</string>
    <string name="fragment_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="fragment_main">Main</string>

    <string name="profile_personal_detail">Personal Detail</string>
    <string name="profile_contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="profile_privacy_security">Privacy and Security</string>
    <string name="profile_preferences">Preferences</string>
    <string name="profile_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_list">List</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_messages">Messages</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_stores">Stores</string>
    <string name="view_store">View Store</string>
    <string name="get_direction">Get Direction</string>
    <string name="upload_image">Upload Image</string>
    <string name="store_list_title">Store List</string>
    <string name="bookmark_list_title">Bookmarks</string>
    <string name="add_to_favorite">Add to favorite</string>
    <string name="remove_from_favorite">Remove</string>
    <string name="favorite">Favorite</string>
    <string name="edit_store">Edit Store</string>
    <string name="save_changes">Save Changes</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change Password</string>
    <string name="current_password">Current Password</string>
    <string name="new_password">New Password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="opening_time">Opening:</string>
    <string name="closing_time">Closing:</string>
    <string name="store_status">Status:</string>
    <string name="store_status_open">Open</string>
    <string name="store_status_closed">Closed</string>
    <string name="first_gulay_store">First Gulay Store</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_content">"Welcome to PampangNav! By using our app, you agree to these terms. Please read them carefully.

**1. Your Account**

You are responsible for your account and anything that happens while you are signed in. Keep your password safe.

**2. Using PampangNav**

Don\'t misuse our services. For example, don’t interfere with our services or try to access them using a method other than the interface and the instructions that we provide. You may use our services only as permitted by law.

**3. Content in PampangNav**

Our service displays some content that is not PampangNav\'s. This content is the sole responsibility of the entity that makes it available. We may review content to determine whether it is illegal or violates our policies, and we may remove or refuse to display content that we reasonably believe violates our policies or the law. But that does not necessarily mean that we review content, so please don’t assume that we do.

**4. About Software in our Services**

PampangNav gives you a personal, worldwide, royalty-free, non-assignable and non-exclusive license to use the software provided to you by PampangNav as part of the services. This license is for the sole purpose of enabling you to use and enjoy the benefit of the services as provided by PampangNav, in the manner permitted by these terms.

**5. Modifying and Terminating our Services**

We are constantly changing and improving our Services. We may add or remove functionalities or features, and we may suspend or stop a Service altogether.

You can stop using our Services at any time, although we’ll be sorry to see you go. PampangNav may also stop providing Services to you, or add or create new limits to our Services at any time.

**6. Warranties and Disclaimers**

We provide our Services using a commercially reasonable level of skill and care and we hope that you will enjoy using them. But there are certain things that we don’t promise about our Services.

OTHER THAN AS EXPRESSLY SET OUT IN THESE TERMS OR ADDITIONAL TERMS, NEITHER PAMPANGNAV NOR ITS SUPPLIERS OR DISTRIBUTORS MAKE ANY SPECIFIC PROMISES ABOUT THE SERVICES. FOR EXAMPLE, WE DON’T MAKE ANY COMMITMENTS ABOUT THE CONTENT WITHIN THE SERVICES, THE SPECIFIC FUNCTIONS OF THE SERVICES, OR THEIR RELIABILITY, AVAILABILITY, OR ABILITY TO MEET YOUR NEEDS. WE PROVIDE THE SERVICES “AS IS”.

**7. Liability for our Services**

WHEN PERMITTED BY LAW, PAMPANGNAV, AND PAMPANGNAV’S SUPPLIERS AND DISTRIBUTORS, WILL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE FOR LOST PROFITS, REVENUES, OR DATA, FINANCIAL LOSSES OR INDIRECT, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES.

**8. About these Terms**

We may modify these terms or any additional terms that apply to a Service to, for example, reflect changes to the law or changes to our Services. You should look at the terms regularly. We’ll post notice of modifications to these terms on this page. Changes will not apply retroactively and will become effective no sooner than fourteen days after they are posted. However, changes addressing new functions for a Service or changes made for legal reasons will be effective immediately. If you do not agree to the modified terms for a Service, you should discontinue your use of that Service.

If you have any questions or concerns about these Terms and Conditions, you can contact us at:

App Name: PampangNav
Email: pampangnav@gmail.com"
</string>
</resources>